Guide to the Duke Family papers on the Duke Farms residence, 1859-2004 and undated RL.01437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Architectural Records, 1897-1992 and undated
  - Farm Barn, 1906, 1985
    - 1/2 in. Detail of Stone Gable & Cupola. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jul 19. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D2F5)
    - Columns, Farm Barn. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jul 19. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D2F5)
    - Truss Details Sheet "A". Kendall, Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jul 19. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D2F5)
    - Truss Details Sheet "B". Kendall, Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jul 19. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D2F5)
    - Truss Details Sheet "C". Kendall, Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jul 19. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D2F5)
    - Truss Details Sheet "D". Kendall, Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jul 19. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D2F5)
    - Plans for Storage Shed, Front Elevation, Rear Elevation. P.C. Van Nuys. Undated. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F9)
    - Plans for Storage Shed, Floor Plan.[ P.C. Van Nuys]. Undated. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F9)
    - Plans for Storage Shed, East End, West End.[ P.C. Van Nuys]. Undated. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F9)